Hello.
こんにちは
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
I am doing.
してます
Don't be nervous.
緊張しないでください
It's cute.
可愛いですね
Your skin is so white.
肌白いね、めっちゃ
Can I ask you a few questions?
ちょっといろいろ質問してもいいですか?
What are you doing now?
今は何してる?
normally.
普段
I'm changing the problem.
問題変えてます
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
What year are you in?
何年生だろう?
1st year student.
1年生
What do you mean now?
いうことは今、いくつ?
I'm 18 years old.
18歳です
You're young.
若いね
I just started school.
入学したばっかりなんだ
fun?
楽しい?
It's fun.
楽しいです
Great, that's the problem.
すごいね、問題なんだ
What are you doing?
何やってるの?
musical instrument.
楽器
I play the piano.
ピアノやってます
It's a piano.
ピアノなんだ
That's amazing.
すごいね
Have you been doing this since you were a child?
子供の頃からやってるの?
結構
Ah, that's right.
あ、 そうなんだ
Do you have any dreams for the future?
何か将来の夢とかあるの?
In the future, I have decided to have a good sense of music.
将来は音楽のセンス内定になっています
That's nice.
いいですね
where?
どこ?
School?
学校?
Elementary school or something.
小学校とか
primary school.
小学校
Well, it seems like something is going on.
えー、何かいそうだよね
Like a beautiful teacher.
美人教師みたいな
Thank you.
ありがとうね
nice.
いいね
Are you currently working part-time?
今バイトやったりしてるの?
I'm working part-time.
バイトやってます
What are you doing?
何やってるの?
I had a part-time job at an ivy shop.
ツタ屋でバイトした
Ivy shop?
ツタ屋?
Why Tsutaya?
なんでツタ屋の?
why?
なんで?
I can't really say anything.
特に言えないです
In particular, aren't you doing some kind of piano work as a part-time job?
特にね、何かピアノのそれ仕事とかはバイト目ではしてないの?
I don't play the piano, but I would like to teach it to small children.
ピアノはしてないんですけど、 ちっちゃい子とかにピアノ教えて
Masu.
ます
Ah, that's right.
あ、 そうなんだ
That's about it, you're good at it.
それぐらいね、上手なんだね
You like little kids, kid.
ちっちゃい子は好きなんだね、子供
I also like small children.
ちっちゃい子供も好きです
Do you like children too?
子供も好き?
I also like children.
子供も好き
Do you have a boyfriend now?
今は彼氏いるの?
I don't have a boyfriend.
彼氏いないんです
Are you not there?
いないの?
Or is there not that many boys at school?
学校はあれか、何かあんまり男子とかいないんですか?
that's right.
そうです
Looks like it's all girls?
女子ばっかりみたいな?
that's right.
そうです
Well, that's how we met.
そっか、出会いがじゃあ
I haven't had any encounters.
出会いもないですね
Hey.
へー
Have you ever had a boyfriend like that?
今までそういう彼氏行ったことはある?
Only one boyfriend.
彼氏一人だけ
Oh, just one person?
あ、一人だけ?
When I was in high school.
高校の時に
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
We were separated.
分かれちゃったんだ
I understand.
分かりましたね
Why did we split up?
なんで分かれちゃったの?
We went to different universities, so we didn't have time to see each other that much.
ちょっと大学が別々になって、あんま会う時間もなくて
Understood.
分 かりました
Did you do that naughty thing with that boyfriend?
その彼氏とはそのエッチなことしてた?
I did.
しました
first time.
初めて
first time?
初めて?
yes.
はい
Oh, how was it?
あ ら、どうだった?
how was it?
どうだった?
good.
よかった
Oh, good?
あ、よかった?
how was it?
どうだった?
It was good.
よかったです
how was it?
どうだった?
It played a nice tone.
素敵な音色を奏でられた
nice tone.
素敵な音色
Didn't it hurt the first time?
初めて痛かったりしてなかったの?
It hurt at first.
最初は痛かったです
Did it hurt at first?
最初は痛かった?
But I guess I'm used to it.
けど、慣れたなみたいな
Okay, so you've done it a few times?
結構じゃあ何回かやってたの?
I agree.
そうですね
It was long.
長かったんで
The time we were together.
付き合ってた時間が
How long have you been together?
どのくらい付き合ってたの?
About 2 years.
2年くらい
Long!
長っ!
It's really weird.
めっちゃいじずなんだね
It's a mess.
いじずなんですね
Ijizu, but unfortunately we were separated.
いじずだけど、ちょっと残念なことに分かれちゃった
That's right.
そうなんだ
Wait, haven't you been doing that lately?
ちょっとじゃあ、最近はじゃあ、そういうことしてない?
What are you doing?
ちょっと何してる?
It's been a while, it's been a while.
ちょっとじゃあ、久々の
Are you nervous?
緊張してます?
Don't be nervous.
緊張しないで
Next time, a lot of things.
次は色々ね、ちょっと
I'll do it.
やっちゃいます
yes.
はい
You have a nice face.
顔っちいね
I went face to face.
顔っちいってきました
It's white.
白いね
yes.
はい
It's white.
白いです
You're not tanned at all, are you?
全然日に焼けてないでしょ?
I'm applying sunburn to my eyes.
日焼けの目塗ってるんで
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
But what?
でも、何?
No, what do you do on your day off?
いや、休み日とか何してるの?
Day off?
休みの日?
I already have a part-time job.
もうバイトです
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Are you sweating?
汗かいてる?
a little bit.
ちょっと
It's hot.
暑いです
hot?
暑い?
Hold on a moment.
ちょっと、つっちゃって
Are you playing the piano with your fingers?
指でピアノ弾いてるの?
that's right.
そうです
nice piano.
素敵なピアノ
It's beautiful.
綺麗だもんね
is that so.
そうですか
It’s been a while.
久々の
It's been a while.
久々です
Since high school.
高校以来
that's right.
そうです
Wow, it's black.
すごい、黒なんだね
what?
何?
I thought it was white because it was white.
白いから、白なのかと思った
It's like a piano.
ピアノみたいになってるね
that's right.
そうです
what happened?
どうしたの?
I hid it.
隠した
You hid it.
隠しましたね
It's a little embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしいです
lie?
嘘?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
You don't know.
知らないでしょ
what?
何?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
TRUE?
本当?
yes.
はい
I'm wearing it more and more, but I'm taking it off.
どんどん着てるけど、脱がしてるよ
It's beautiful, nose.
綺麗だね、鼻
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's getting hot in here.
ここ、体温かくなって
You're really shy.
めっちゃ恥ずかしがってるじゃん
Have a naughty chew.
エッチなチューする
Are you going to have such a naughty chew?
そんなエッチなチューするの?
Is it in the picture?
写ってるの?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
cute.
可愛い
Do you want to take it off?
脱 ぎたいの?
I don't want to take it off.
脱ぎたくない
Do you want to take it off?
脱 ぎたいの?
cute.
可愛い
You have a nice butt.
良いおしりしてるね
That's really sexy.
すごいセクシーだね
I want this to be a beautiful card.
これ、綺麗なカードしたいね
It's so beautiful.
すごい綺麗だね
Which one?
どっち?
Are both beautiful?
どっちも綺麗なの?
That's amazing.
すごいね
what
なん
And is it that beautiful?
で そんなに綺麗なの?
amazing.
すごい
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
That's amazing.
すごいね
Just a moment before that.
ちょっと、その前に
It feels really good though.
めっちゃ気持ちいいんだけど
why?
なんで?
No way, it's tight.
まさか、きつい
It's so tight I can't get it in.
きつくて入んないんだけど
amazing.
すごい
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
It's really tough.
すごいきついね
Good.
よいしょ
This feels so good.
これ、すげー気持ちいい
It feels so good.
めちゃくちゃ気持ちいい
It feels really good though.
すごく気持ちいいんだけど
What should I do?
どうしよう
terrible.
やばい
This is amazing.
すごいこれ
It feels so good.
すげー気持ちいい
Will you win another one?
もう1個当たる?
Won?
当たる?
You look really comfortable.
すごい気持ちいい顔してるね
Yes, wait a minute.
はい、ちょっと待って
I'll end up getting hurt though.
傷になっちゃうんだけど
Wait, that's different.
ちょっと、違う
I get into a position
体勢になっちゃう
kana.
かな
wait a minute.
ちょっと 待って
Anno?
あんの?
There is, right?
あるでしょ
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Does it cost that much?
そんなにかかる?
amazing.
すごい
Move it in and out slowly.
ゆっくり出し入れして
Please hold it.
かかえてね
This is really tight.
すごい締まるね、これ
You're serious about this, right?
本 気でしょ、これ
Can I take it out?
出していい?
Leave it like this.
このまま
Do you think you can have a child?
子供出来ちゃうと思う?
Is it okay?
いいの?
Looks like it's out?
出してらしい?
Go ahead.
行ってこら
Take it inside.
中に出して
I cum inside you.
中に出しちゃったよ
Is it okay?
いいの?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
He told me to let him out.
出 してって言ってた
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
It's really tight.
すごい締まるね
When we first met.
最初に会った時と
Play harmony.
ハーモニーを奏でて